(Sheldon:)Leonard, this is my Meemaw.
(Leonard:)Hi. So nice
to finally meet you.
(Leonard:)Let me take this
for you, Meemaw.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)No. Oh, no.
Now you call her “Constance.”
I call her “Meemaw.”
(Sheldon:)You have your own Meemaw.
(Sheldon:)It's not my fault
she died when you were four.
(Meemaw:)Is that nice to say
to your friend?
(Sheldon:)It isn't, Meemaw.
(Sheldon:)Sorry, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Can you please
live with us forever?
Oh. (laughs)
That's ridiculous!
If you had
(Howard:)a superpower,
and spent your whole life
(Howard:)being told to suppress it,
(Howard:)when you finally decide
to embrace that power,
why hide in isolation?!
(Raj:)I'm sorry,
(Raj:)and how much money did
your version of Frozen make?!
(Howard:)I'm just saying,
instead of “Let it Go,”
she should really sing,
“Look At Me Hiding in a Freezer
Like a Dove Bar.”
(Raj:)She built an ice castle,
made a snow monster
(Raj:)and gave herself
a complete makeover in one day.
(Raj:)You know what I saw
you do today?
(Raj:)Eat a block of cream cheese
straight from the foil